Toggle navigation [](https://www.makesurveymoney.com/default.asp)

#### Union Street Enterprises, Inc. Privacy Policy

Please [click here](https://www.makesurveymoney.com/privacy-policy.pdf) for a printable PDF version of this notice.

\[Effective Date: 5/22/2024\]

Union Street Enterprises, Inc. (“Company”) collects, uses, and shares information about you when you interact with our surveys, websites, social media sites and handles, and email (our “Services”). This Privacy Policy explains:

* the types of [information we collect](#infowecollect) through our Services;
* [how we use](#howweuse) and protect that information;
* the types of information we may [share with others](#howweshare) and under what circumstances;
* the [choices you have](#optionsandrights) regarding our collection, use, and sharing practices; and
* details regarding [our use of third-party cookies](#automatically) and other tracking technologies.

We also include special disclosures related to the state privacy laws of California, Virginia, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, Nevada, Texas, Oregon and Montana.

This Policy applies when you interact with us through our Services. It also applies anywhere it is linked. It does not apply to non-Company websites and mobile applications that may link to the Services or be linked to from the Services; please review the privacy policies on those websites and applications directly to understand their privacy practices.

**Information We Collect**

Information you give us

Our Services may permit you to enter contact information and other information about you. We collect and store any information you enter on our Services. This includes:

* Contact and demographic information, including information you enter when you respond to one of our advertisements on third-party websites.
* Your photograph.
* Information you provide when you complete a survey administered by us.
* Information you provide when you participate in a contest or sweepstakes that we offer.
* If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence and any contact information provided.
* Medical or health information that you provide to us in the course of responding to a survey.
* Information we may request from you to enable you to be paid for your participation in a survey, including a W9 form (Request for Taxpayer Identification) if you meet certain earnings thresholds.
* You may be pre-registered for our site(s) when you sign up on a third party website if you give consent for that explicitly or through agreeing to such third party website’s privacy policy.

Information We Collect From Other Sources

We may also receive information about you from other parties:

* Your responses to questions that our market research partners may ask you for survey qualification purposes.
* Information from PayPal, if you choose to use PayPal to receive payment from us. This information does not include your payment card or other financial data.
* Information about your interests, activities, and employment history from social networks and other places where you choose to share information publicly.
* Information about your interaction with advertisements on our Services, or that we place on third party websites, from online advertising companies.

If you decide to invite others to the Services, we will collect your and the other persons’ names, email addresses, and/or phone numbers in order to send an email or text message and follow up with the other person. You agree that you will obtain the other person’s consent before giving us his or her contact information. You also agree that you will not send us the contact information of a minor. We will inform any other person you invite that you gave us his or her information in the invitation email.

Information We Collect Automatically

When you interact with the Services, we collect certain information about your use of our Services automatically. This includes:

* Analytics about your interaction with our Services, including traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, the resources that you access, and how you reached our Services.
* Details regarding the device you use to access our Services, including, but not limited to, your IP address, operating system, and browser type.
* Information about how you interact with our ads and newsletters, including whether you open or click links in any correspondence.
* Information that you make available to us on a social media platform (such as by clicking on a social media icon linked from our Services), including your account ID or username and other information included in your posts.

Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

We use cookies and other technologies to provide features on our Services. We also partner with other companies that use these technologies to collect information about your use of our Services and responses to our advertisements on our behalf.

The types of cookies and tracking technologies our partners use can be categorized as:

* Analytics: These technologies help us to understand how visitors interact with our Services by collecting and reporting information about how you and your device interact with the Services.
* Advertising: These technologies allow us to serve relevant advertising to you on other websites or apps.

Below is a list of these partners with links to more information about their use of your information and any options they may make available regarding tracking.

| Category | Partner | Further Information |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Advertising | Microsoft/Bing Ads | [Privacy Policy](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement) / [Opt-out](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-US/) |
| Advertising; Analytics | Google | [Google Privacy and Terms](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites?hl=en-US) |
| Advertising | Facebook | [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php) / [Opt-out](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217) |
| Analytics | Mixpanel | [Privacy Policy](https://mixpanel.com/legal/privacy-policy/) / [Opt-out](http://preferences-mgr.trustarc.com/) |
| Analytics | Inspectlet | [Privacy Policy](https://www.inspectlet.com/terms-of-service#privacy) |
| Analytics | Imperium | [Privacy Policy](https://www.imperium.com/privacy/) |
| Analytics | Stackadapt | [Privacy Policy](https://www.stackadapt.com/privacy-policy) |
| Advertising | NotifyAI | [Privacy Policy](https://notifyai.io/privacy.html) |
| Account Security/Authentication | Twilio | [Privacy Policy](https://www.twilio.com/en-us/legal/privacy) |

**How We Use Your Information**

We may use the information we collect about you for the following purposes:

* To provide you with our products and services, including to take steps to enter into a contract for sale or for services, process payments, fulfill orders or the terms of an agreement we have with you, send service communications, handle customer support requests, and conduct general business operations such as accounting, recordkeeping, and audits.
* To give recommendations, deliver our newsletter, deliver personalized marketing and advertising to you about our products and services, and to enable additional features on our Services and to provide you with a personalized service.
* To improve your experience on the Services and improve and grow our business, including to understand how our Services are being used, understand our customer base, understand the effectiveness of our marketing, and develop new products and services.
* To deliver tailored advertising on our Services and on third-party websites based on your preferences or interests and measures the effectiveness of ads.
* To protect and secure our Services, assets, network, and business operations, and to detect, investigate, and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be fraudulent or illegal.
* To comply with legal process, such as warrants, subpoenas, court orders, and lawful regulatory or law enforcement requests and to comply with legal requirements regarding the provision of products and services.

Our Leaderboards: Some of our websites display your first initial, last name, photograph (if you’ve uploaded one) and city on a leaderboard. To opt out of the leaderboard, please log in to your account and click “Account Overview” from the personal menu at the top right of the screen. Under “Public Profile”, check the “Opt out of Leader Boards” checkbox.

**How We Secure the Information We Collect From or About You**

We use a combination of physical, technical, and administrative safeguards to protect the information we collect through the Services. While we use these precautions to safeguard your information, we cannot guarantee the security of the networks, systems, servers, devices, and databases we operate or that are operated on our behalf.

**How We Share Your Information**

Service Providers: We engage vendors to perform functions on our behalf, and they may receive information about you. These vendors are obligated by contract to use information that we share only for the purpose of providing these services. The business functions our vendors support are:

* Billing, collection, and payment.
* Auditing and accounting.
* Professional services.
* Analytics.
* Security.
* Information technology support, including cloud storage, software-as-a-service, and business software.
* Marketing emails.

Market Research Partners: We disclose information about you to the organizations that provide the surveys we make available to you on our Services. We and they use this information to administer the surveys and gauge your interest in, and suggest, other surveys.

Co-registration Partners and Agencies: We may disclose information about you to our co-registration partners and agencies to streamline your registration with them.

Postal Mailings: We disclose information about you to reputable third-party organizations for purposes of delivering relevant marketing offers by postal mail.

Advertisers: We may disclose information about you to advertisers who place ads on our Services. Specifically, we may prepopulate an ad requesting contact information from you with the contact information we obtained from you (but we only send this information if you click through on that ad). We also partner with companies (including the ones listed in the table above) that assist us in advertising our Services to you and others who may be interested in them, and who use cookies to display interest-based advertising to you on our Services and third-party websites and apps. These companies may use tracking technologies on our website to collect or receive information from the Services and elsewhere on the internet and then use that information to measure and target ads.

Corporate Affiliates: We share data with other members of our group of companies.

Social Media Platforms: Where you choose to interact with us through social media, your interaction with these programs typically allows the social media company to collect some information about you through digital cookies they place on your device and other tracking mechanisms they place on your device. In some cases, the social media company may recognize you through its digital cookies even when you do not interact with its application. Please visit the social media companies’ respective privacy policies to better understand their data collection practices and the controls they make available to you.

Cross-Device Advertising: We may use third-party advertising companies to target advertisements to you on our Services, across the web, on your mobile device, or on any of your other devices, based on the information we have collected from and about you, as well as information relating to your and other users' visits to this and other websites and online services. To do so, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser (including using pixel tags) or recognize an identifier associated with your mobile device. These companies may also use these technologies, along with personal information they or we collect on the different devices you use, to recognize you across the devices you use, such as a mobile device and a laptop or other computer. To learn about your choices in connection with these practices on the particular device on which you are accessing this policy, please visit [//www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt\_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) and [//www.aboutads.info/choices](https://www.aboutads.info/choices) to opt out in desktop and mobile web browsers. You may download the AppChoices app at [//www.aboutads.info/appchoices](https://www.aboutads.info/appchoices) to opt out in mobile apps. You may also click on the informational icon contained within each interest based ad.

In Response to Legal Process: We share data when we believe in good faith that we are lawfully authorized or required to do so to respond to lawful subpoenas, warrants, court orders, or other regulatory or law enforcement requests.

**Additional Information about Our Data Collection and Sharing Practices**

Sharing of Aggregated or De-Identified Data

We may use and share at our discretion data that has been aggregated (information that has been compiled into summaries) or de-identified (information that has been stripped of all unique identifiers such that it cannot be linked to a particular individual).

Combination of Information

We may combine information from the Services together and with other information we obtain from our business records. Additionally, information collected about you from a particular browser or device may be linked to information collected from another computer or device that we believe relates to you.

Change of Ownership or Corporate Organization

We may transfer to another entity or its affiliates or service providers some or all information about you in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, acquisition, sale of assets or any line of business, change in ownership control, or financing transaction. We cannot promise that an acquiring party or the merged entity will have the same privacy practices or treat your information as described in this Policy.

Cross-border Transfer of Data

If you use our Services outside of the United States, you understand that we may collect, process, and store your information in the United States and other countries. The laws in the United States regarding information may be different from the laws of your country. Any such transfers will comply with safeguards as required by relevant law. By using the Services, you consent to the collection, international transfer, storage, and processing of your data.

Our Practices Regarding Information Belonging to Children

The Services are intended for users age thirteen and older. Company does not knowingly collect information from children. If we discover that we have inadvertently collected information from anyone younger than the age of 13, we will delete that information.

Sharing of Medical or Health Information

To the extent that we receive protected health information about you, that information is subject to electronic disclosure to the extent permitted by applicable law.

**Your Options and Rights Regarding Your Information**

Your Account: Please visit your account page by logging in to your account and selecting “Account Overview” from the personal menu at the top right of the screen to update your contact information. Choose “Select payment method” from the personal menu to select the method you use to receive payment.

Email Unsubscribe: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email newsletter, or [Contact Us](https://www.makesurveymoney.com/contactus.asp) and we will promptly remove you from all correspondence.

Ad Choices: You can learn more about ad serving companies and the options available to limit their collection and use of your information by visiting the websites for the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) and the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/choices). Similarly, you can learn about your options to opt out of mobile app tracking by certain advertising networks through your device settings and by resetting the advertiser ID on your Apple or Android device.

Please note that opting out of advertising networks services does not mean that you will not receive advertising while using our Services or on other websites, nor will it prevent the receipt of interest-based advertising from other companies that do not participate in these programs. It will, however, exclude you from interest-based advertising conducted through participating networks, as provided by their policies and choice mechanisms. If you delete your cookies, you may also delete your opt-out preferences.

You can control cookies using your web browser’s settings. If you delete your cookies or if you set your browser to decline cookies, some features of the Sites may not be available, work, or work as designed.

Your browser or device may include “Do Not Track” functionality. We do not honor Do Not Track signals at this time.

Our Leaderboards: Some of our websites display your first initial, last name, photograph (if you’ve uploaded one) and city on a leaderboard. To opt out of the leaderboard, please log in to your account and click “Account Overview” from the personal menu at the top right of the screen. Under “Public Profile”, check the “Opt out of Leader Boards” checkbox.

**Additional Privacy Rights Based on State Laws California, Virginia, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, Texas, Oregon and Montana**

Texas Privacy Notice

Per the Texas Digital Privacy Act (TDPA), this shall serve as notice that Union Street may sell your sensitive data pursuant to the policies elaborated in the “Right to Know About Sources of Personal Information and Personal Information Disclosed or Sold” section of the privacy policy below. You do have the right to opt-out, as explained in the “Right to Opt Out of Sale of Personal Information to Third Parties” section.

California Shine the Light

Residents of the State of California have the right to request information from Company regarding third parties to whom we have disclosed certain categories of information during the preceding year for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes. [Contact Us](https://www.makesurveymoney.com/contactus.asp) to make such a request.

California, Virginia, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, Texas, Oregon & Montana Privacy Laws

The CCPA, CVDPA, CPA, CTCPA, UTCPA, TDPA, OCPA, and MCDPA, are the relevant state privacy laws of California, Virginia, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, Texas, Oregon and Montana, respectively, which provide residents of these states, and residents outside of these states, with rights to receive certain disclosures regarding the collection, use, and sharing of information about them, as well as rights to know/access, delete, and limit sharing of personal information. You have the right to be free from discrimination based on your exercise of your rights under these laws.

To the extent that we collect Personal Information that is subject to the CCPA, CVDPA, CPA, CTCPA, UTCPA, TDPA, OCPA, and MCDPA, that information, our practices, and your rights are described below.

**Notice at Collection Regarding the Categories of Personal Information Collected**

You have the right to receive notice of the categories of Personal Information we collect, and the purposes for which we use Personal Information. The categories we use below to describe Personal Information are those enumerated in the CCPA. We collect this Personal Information for the purposes described in the How We Use Your Information section above.

* Personal Identifiers:
    * We collect your name, phone number, email address and contact address when you create an account or otherwise disclose that information to us, for example by providing it in response to an ad on a third-party website. If you choose to create an account, we will assign one or more unique identifiers to your profile.
    * We collect your social media handle and basic account information when you interact with our Services through social media.
    * We collect a unique numerical identifier, assigned to you by a first-party cookie, automatically when you use our Services.
    * You may submit information to us to enable us to process payments to you.
    * We may collect health information about you if you are responding to a health-related survey or if you are completing health-related qualification questions which could enable you to qualify for certain surveys.
    * We collect your IP address and other device information automatically when you use our Services.
* Protected Classifications: We collect your age in order to comply with laws that restrict collection and disclosure of personal information belonging to minors. We may collect your gender, race, ethnic origin, disability status, and sexual orientation in the context of a survey or during our profiling process where we ask you qualification questions in order to determine which surveys you match with.
* Commercial Information: When you engage in transactions with us, we create records related to our payments to you and the surveys you have taken.
* Internet or Other Electronic Network Activity Information: We collect information about your browsing history, search history, and interactions with websites, and/or applications advertisements automatically when you use our Services.
* Geolocation Data: As described above, we collect your IP address automatically when you use our Services. We may be able to determine your general location based on the IP address. We do not collect your precise location (e.g., your GPS coordinates).
* Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information: If you contact us via phone, we may record the call. We will notify you if a call is being recorded at the beginning of the call. We may collect your image.
* Professional or employment-related information: We may collect information about your current employer and your employment history when you apply for a job with us.
* Education information: We may collect information about the institutions you have attended and the level of education you have attained when you apply for a job with us.
* Inferences drawn to create a profile about a consumer reflecting the consumer’s preferences or characteristics: We may analyze your preferences based on the surveys you take and the information we and our partners gather when you interact with our Services.

Our practices regarding the disclosure and sale of your Personal Information are described below. To opt-out of the sale of your Personal Information, please visit our “Do Not Sell My Personal Information” page [here](https://www.makesurveymoney.com/dnsmpi.asp).

**Right to Know About Sources of Personal Information and Personal Information Disclosed or Sold**

During the preceding 12 months, we have disclosed for business purposes and/or sold the following categories of personal information to the following categories of recipients:

| Personal Information | Disclosed | Sold | Sources | Recipients |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Personal Identifiers: | Yes | Yes | You | Market Research Partners; Co-registration partners or agencies; Postal Advertisers; Cross-Device Advertising Companies |
| Payment Information: | Yes | No  | You | Payment providers |
| Protected Classifications: | Yes | Yes | You | Market Research Partners; Co-registration partners or agencies |
| Commercial Information: | Yes | No  | You | Market Research Partners |
| Geolocation Information: | Yes | Yes | You | Market Research Partners; Companies involved in Advertising |
| Internet or Electronic Network Activity Information: | Yes | Yes | You | Market Research Partners; Companies involved in Advertising |
| Audio, Electronic, Visual, Thermal, Olfactory, or Similar Information: | No  | No  | You | Market Research Partners |
| Professional or Employment-Related Information: | Yes | Yes | You | Market Research Partners; Co-registration partners or agencies |
| Education Information: | Yes | Yes | You | Market Research Partners; Co-registration partners or agencies |
| Inferences Drawn About You: | Yes | No  | You; Market Research Partners | Market Research Partners |

Entities to whom we disclose information for business purposes are service providers, which are companies that we engage to conduct activities on our behalf. Service providers are restricted from using Personal Information for any purpose that is not related to our engagement.

Entities to whom we “sell” information are third parties. Under the CCPA, CVDPA, CPA, CTCPA, UTCPA, TDPA, OCPA, and MCDPA, a business “sells” personal information when it discloses it to a company for monetary or other benefit. A company may be considered a third party either because the purpose for its sharing of personal information is not for an enumerated business purpose under California, Virginia, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, Texas, Oregon, or Montana, law, or because its contract does not restrict it from using personal Information for other purposes.

**Right to Opt Out of Sale of Personal Information to Third Parties**

You have the right to opt out of any sale of your Personal Information by Company to third parties.

To exercise your right to opt out of the sale of your Personal Information, please visit our “[Do Not Sell My Personal Information](https://www.makesurveymoney.com/dnsmpi.asp)” webpage.

Please note that your right to opt out does not apply to our sharing of Personal Information with service providers.

We may also disclose information to other entities who are not listed here when required by law or to protect our Company or other persons, as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Right to Know and Request Access to and Deletion of Personal Information**

You have the right to request access to Personal Information collected about you and information regarding the source of that Personal Information, the purposes for which we collect it, and the third parties and service providers with whom we share it. You also have the right to request in certain circumstances that we delete Personal Information that we have collected directly from you. We may have a reason under the law why we do not have to comply with your request, or why we may comply with it in a more limited way than you anticipated. If we do, we will explain that to you in our response.

How to Submit an Access or Deletion Request

You may submit a request to exercise your rights to know/access or delete your personal information by [Contacting Us](https://www.makesurveymoney.com/contactus.asp).

You may authorize another individual or a business, called an authorized agent, to make requests on your behalf through these means.

Verification Procedures

In order to process your request to know/access or delete Personal Information we collect, disclose, or sell, we must verify your request. We verify your identity by asking you to provide personal identifiers we can match against information we may have collected from you previously and confirm your request using the email or telephone account stated in the request.

We will not use Personal Information we collect in connection with verifying or responding to your request for any purpose other than responding to your request.

**Special Information for Job Applicants**

When you apply for a job with Company, we collect certain information about you as outlined in this Policy. Information may be collected about you in multiple ways: you may provide it to us in connection with your application; we may make observations in the application process or collect information from public information sources; or you may authorize us to collect information from other sources, such as a former employer or reference. In certain circumstances, you may submit your application for employment through a third-party service that displays our job posting. We do not control the privacy practices of these third-party services. Please review their privacy policies carefully prior to submitting your application materials.

**Special Information for Nevada Residents**

Residents of the State of Nevada have the right to opt out of the sale of certain pieces of their information to other companies who will sell or license their information to others. Company does not engage in such sales. If you are a Nevada resident and would like more information about our data sharing practices, please [Contact Us](https://www.makesurveymoney.com/contactus.asp).

**Changes to This Policy**

We may make changes to this Policy from time to time. The “Effective Date” at the top of this page indicates when this Privacy Policy was last revised. We may also notify you in other ways from time to time about the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information described in this Policy.

For questions about our privacy practices, please [Contact Us](https://www.makesurveymoney.com/contactus.asp), or write to us at:

Union Street Enterprises, Inc.  
PO Box 4668 #23563  
New York, NY 10163-4668

© 2024 Union Street Enterprises, Inc.
